Members only emojis. Oh, I wonder is ASAP
Anybody knows any
Wispered her name in the temples of night
Golden wings glow
stands where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to
venom in the same breath said but the fire in his eyes burns gold
some cats, some tarot cards, and maybe like a beat ahead or I don't know we can have different
people that are on this show, I don't know. No. DJ Electra, I'll ask Electra when she, I'll ask
Electra, yeah she might, she might be able to help out. Love Electra. Smelly's a member,
Good to see you. Hopefully everyone's doing good
You losing my likes well, it's okay, you know, I know just
You know, I don't want to take any risks
Let me try to protect this channel, but the audio wasn't too good and I was, you know,
you know fresh.
Drinking on now. I say I seen you got a couple different beers earlier. They sounded like crazy fruity drinks now
What yeah IPA?
Yeah, it's like
Taste Bud you got dude. Well, it's nine percent alcohol. And so that's like, you know, yeah, that's like beer, right though
Yeah, it's a beer. It's like a very strong beer
Yeah, it's not very good, but I'm good. Yeah, I don't look like a beer drinker. I have a fruit punch in the fridge
I make a hard fruit punch and stuff like that. I just think I used to drink I used to drink like a whole thing of vodka
a whole bottle of vodka and like a whole
Gallon of orange juice, but I was I got a little too wild and
You don't think you don't say yeah. Yeah
You got a little twisted off of a few nine percent, huh?
How many how many beers does it take you to get drunk?
It takes like I can drink like three of these in a night. I'll be good and stuff like that drinks from my mama
Okay, no way. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Jamie. I'm sorry, Jamie. I'm sorry, Jamie
You still drinks for your mama?
Yeah, cheers dude. I'm sorry, Jamie. Jamie. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to bring him back
I thought he calmed down, but he's been quiet, but yeah, he was totally inappropriate, but I love you, Jamie
And thank you for being on the show. Okay
Love you to Jamie. No hard feelings, baby. You're beautiful, okay?
Sorry about that, um, it's okay
You're not fat. You're not ugly. It's just me
Baby, what else happened so I didn't care about you right now
So someone called me on my phone and uh, they were like, uh doing like the jimmy, uh
And then I think they like three way to be with jimmy and the jimmy is like, who's this? Who's this?
And I'm not talking to Jimmy right now. So it was like very, very awkward.
So there was that. Do you know who Jimmy is, Alex?
I think so. Some black kid, right, Jimmy, something.
He's got a cardboard box like on his window behind him.
Black kid, a black kid.
Yeah, some fat black kid. What do you want me to say?
That's who Jimmy is. The fuck.
You know, he's not a kid, he's not a kid.
He's a bad black kid.
Is he gay?
He's gay
Jimmy they came on my no, I'm not a baby. I love pussy
Last time you got it. You love pussy. You love what do you want to know? What do you might say?
Pitch is fucking interested in all aspects of my life, baby. I
Want to why why you so interested in what outside the McQueen does and what he doesn't do
That's the question we should be, you know, asking why are you so interested in what I fucking do?
Alexander McQueen, we've been watching you on a daily basis, hit on psych in multiple different ways.
Oh, good, good. Have you been coordinating? Have you been jotting things down? Keep watching, bro.
Yeah, keep watching. Good, good.
Good for you, bro. Do you like being identified as a homosexual?
Shut up. Your voice is homosexual, bro. Yo, brother, your brain is mush.
Do you know that? You've been on the internet war dog for years. You haven't left that chair. You change your shirt once.
Your brain is mush, asshole, and we all see it. Motherfucker.
So shut the fuck up. Get tough with me. Mutual microphone, bitch boy.
You know, it's like now that I'm looking at this logo. I'm not sure about it
Kind of looks like the cat or dog. You've been on the internet for 10 years. You haven't changed your shoulder left that fucking chair
You're a dirty fuck your brain is mush and the whole YouTube community sees it brother
And the story that made Alex, did you buy that gun that's on your chest with your fake profile picture?
I mean, if that is your wardrobe, have you left that chair in 10 years to fuck up?
Oh, excuse me, 10 years, the motherfucker said 10 years.
Imagine me sitting in the same chair for 10 years.
Well, I mean, that happens, um, you know, that happened on like a true crime thing.
I just agree with you to chair Alex, Alex, you know, what's the great thing about the
true story?
If I were to ask you to sniff my seat as I've been sitting in this chair for 10 years, you'd
The logo is like my seat there. I can make as much. Okay. Well
The logo needs work, but yeah, but you know what? It's like, you know, it's it's I'm just trying to get out
I the first one I made I just made on AI and then I'm sass me this and I and I he he redid it and it's pretty cool
I like it. I like it up there. It's like, you know, but it's like, you know
I'll probably always change things up and stuff like that
But I enjoy I appreciate a lot of people like, you know, he like he did it
You have no fucking
Resolution of anything dude. You're fucking why it doesn't like you brother record. You're not doesn't even like you
recollection
There looks cool there
It's hard to see under on the black background, but it's like
prequel there
What's in this background got an alien you have some
Christmas lights
Yes, I got everything under the sun. I'm a hoarder. I love things. I love technology
Oh, you like
How would I how did you find my channel and what brought what brought you here psych stop it?
No, I'm just wondering what brought like how'd you find the channel right now?
What brought you here?
I've been I've been hearing I've been hearing like people been telling us like streamers to raid my chat and stuff
Like I'm just wondering what happened that what brought you I'm not about rain your chat, dude. Okay. It's okay
You do okay. I don't have a channel anymore. Why is everyone calling me war dog, dude?
Okay, I don't know but you do have a setup. You know everything you probably better set up than I do right now and so
Well, you know, maybe if you'd listen to your
$200 donation friend, maybe he can
Tell you a few more things
Who's that you're talking about? Alex
No, no, no, no, you know, I heard you donated to $200
You know Joker already said that
That he went to Piranha, not me. He said he said and Piranha charged him back that money
You already you already said that we did not meet me
He might have said he might said my name accidentally, but he met Piranha. I don't know how they got it's confused
But I never sent him a dime
Hey big Rob come come join up with your goofy ass microphone
Come talk to us. You got so much to say in chat
You say, I'm Syrax's boyfriend now?
That's fucking funny as fuck.
Imagine me having any contact information
to talk to that goofy bastard.
I'm just saying, there's a lot of streamers
that just have shown up here, and it's like,
with no context for me.
I'm not a streamer.
I'm not a streamer no more, OK?
OK, OK, got you, I got you.
But you kind of like.
burden bridges I've broken right well me too but but when you came I guess that
question you kind of you kind of started smirking and laughing a little bit like
there's something
what was that burden bridging you broken
Clumsy, when are you gonna start calling me out by my name?
No, no, no, no, not for freaking me. It's down.
Clumsy, there's no way you're telling me that I'm all about talking to men.
You have only joined panels that are full of men. There's no way you're coming at me right now.
There ain't no way you're coming at me right now, Clumsy.
All you do is join panels with men.
You're obsessed with men clumsy
You got broomed by a fucking
Multiple goddamn fucking cellmates, dude
Get the fuck out of here with your fucking nonsense, dude
Tell me I'm talking to all I want to do is talk to men
Oh my god, smile again your war dog smile again, you toothless fuck this guy's missing teeth all over the place
Yo, you haven't left that chair and you definitely haven't been to a dentist. Oh my god. Yeah, look at you toothless freak
What oh oh my god?
Something sweet Alexandra
I just think it has no teeth bro. Look at him with his little shoulders. No teeth having freak.
I got a microphone in the dirty hat for 10 years. I haven't left this chair in 10 years
and I have no teeth. That's scary bro. Yeah, shake that head. You like it up and down.
Show us your teeth. Smile for us right now. Take your big boy. Your big boy. Show us your
Just showed you my teeth. You're talking about fucking nonsense, dude
I like shit. What's your teeth? Smile for me again faggot homeboy. Smile us you toothless fuck
You don't leave that chair for nothing, bro. Not even the dentist. That's crazy
Please don't make me sad with all this look at his fucking he looks touchin yo touch that toothless chin
With that dirty beard. There's no teeth in that mouth. He's got four teeth in the front the rest are gone
oh my god you look at that your tooth was fucked your tooth was fucked
lamin about fucking nonsense right now
you understand that i just showed my fucking full mouth
yo bro you gotta get to the dentist get some dentures do something my man
get out of that chair toothless boy 30 fuck
no you're so dirty your teeth are rotting out of your face on youtube
I bet in a year you won't even have front teeth your teeth are running out of your mouth on the live
Look at you. No two's on the right. No two's on the left. Look at him. Yo, he's got three teeth in the front. That's it
Holy shit
Imagine me still having a prettier smile than you will ever have because you are a yeah
Yeah, whatever to the streak. Look at you. Yeah, you got no teeth, bro
You don't get out of that chair look in the mirror take that hat off. I bet you're bored
I bet you're bored too. You're bored. Aren't you?
No teeth don't need to chair Wow
Okay, what's wrong with him? Um, I think he's like I think he's sort of a lot of coke
You think that's legal in the the Academy
I mean you already said you like you like that you like got 25 run to 25 to life or like
20 kilos or something like that and then he then he was accepted the police academy. I'm just a little suspicious about that
You are you a little sister just
Little psych
It's the same shit
Just tell us when you know
You joining to talk to males on a regular basis whatever panel it might be
That's what you're gonna be about you literally enjoy talking to males clumsy. Please stop coming after me broke
I know. I know. I know. I know.
But they say, hold on, let me get back up to camera.
You're a little low, psyche, you're a little low.
What up, Chad?
What up, everybody?
Sorry, I don't see the camera, I don't remember.
Okay, let me see if I can get back a little bit.
Shout out to Trigga, what up, Paul, Jamie Cowboy.
Fuckin low key shout out to everybody in the motherfucking building hit the like subscribe get all notifications for your boys psyches awakened Terry
You're her
Pat that was cute, but it's like, you know, I'm really like
Dropping like pretty much the tarot from the company name because I only have that you're like your problems. Have you low?
Okay, hold on
Please wait connected in a moment
What up everybody man, what up? We don't love that. We don't love that man. Everybody out. Why everybody just saying him let him do this reviews
Like he got content. He makes his own content. It's good that he's reviewing his shit
But you know what psyche when you do the reviews start giving commentary about it now now that you're on the review motion of your own product
They come and tell you about what you don't like and what you do like what you like us. He like see when he said this
I should have did this, you know, give you know, like I'm just trying. I'm just give me thoughts up them throwing it out
There I'm not telling you what to do like always. I'm just always throwing options
Say hi, baby. Say hi. Say hi to the world, baby. Hi child. How's everybody doing?
How are you?
Very good. I wanted like maybe they do
I want to do like the you know the reading if you want me to do one for her or for yourself easy like the special one
I'm doing right now. I'll do I'll take one now. And um, if she's about the whole wash up. So oh
I'll take one if you want to offer one down mind
Man she
Volume yeah, that's yeah, yeah, actually chat chat. Yo, is this volume low?
Is there any more we fuck a roller for you
Okay test it does everyone hear me
I hear you're just a little better. Just a little to my TV is crackling
I hate my I don't know what's what made it crackle all of a sudden one day when I was like I
Put in the computer and suffer them. There's a VR or something on my last
Didn't work, but then it's now everything crackles. I don't know why it's like I've like tried a couple HDMI cores and stuff
That's unfortunate, but I like this this isn't like a lot brighter for my readings and stuff like that
And it's like oh, no, I don't have no ground out Carol. Who the fuck asked me that?
Oh, yeah, I was wondering about that was me that
But yeah, well, you know, it's okay because like yeah, I don't have a runner account either because
Those websites are dangerous. Oh shit. Okay, so easy. What's just popped out? Okay, so you're super defensive right now
This is like the seven of wands and you're like on guard and you feel like this is like
Trapped but who is the monster and it has like this one guy he's being persecuted by all these people and it's like are they the monster
He's the monster because he's Frankenstein, but it's like maybe they both have monstrous qualities
Maybe they both have good qualities maybe like I don't know there's different things
But you like regardless you feel like you're under attack. You haven't been very much injured
So you have a lot of energy for this attack and you can take on a bunch of zombies and stuff like that
Just be careful
You don't want to take on like too many people that are your equal strength or greater because like you're one of you
Thank you, I really think you've done a lot of zombies, but it's like, you know, it's like, you want to, you need to strengthen numbers or something else that you're trying to do.
Okay, also, suit of pentacles that looks like, okay, so this is going to be the seven of pentacles, and so this is like, this is like the harvest time, this is like, there's a lot of hands coming out of the ground, like, I think the queen is back on the earth, and so all of the, everyone's rising from the dead and stuff like that, they're ready.
Everyone's waiting for this time where like, you know, the queen comes back.
It's a Seven of Pentacles, a harvest coming, and a celebration for something, okay?
What else?
Oh, we have this one that says, the king of wands.
They're coming up maybe as a king of wands.
Maybe this would look like you a little bit.
There you go.
No, I think we'll maybe get this one.
It says, but it says vision.
Sorry.
This vision, honor, ultimate masculine energy, and it says leadership.
Oh Mason's here. Hold on one second. Have you met Mason? That's easy. So that's it easy. I hope you like that
You're gonna become no, I heard
Yeah, the wild guy, yeah, he'd be mad at you all the time here right there
No, I didn't make him. I didn't make yourself up or did I kick you up accidentally?
Hey psyche
Is that a picture of you or are you sitting there? Hello? Hey psyche
Me so yeah
You hear me now
Yeah
Psyche yes, what's going on with you?
Well, what's been going on what's been going on with you?
Where's your alien at Psyche you had an alien last night you still have that alien that
Right there peeking out of the behind the couch
Yeah, well whatever happened it's like you whatever happened to your friend too though the other guy we were talking to last night
The thing the guy named the thing oh, yeah thing that is I don't know where he went he was here earlier a little bit like but he
I've been showing past episodes because I just started doing this show like you know pretty much other in the panels earlier this year in January
I mean, so I'm doing it about eight nine months and
It's um, it's finally like you know
I'm able to like go back and look at all these drunk nights that I was like so drunk that I forgot and like I was like
Not paying attention to people and I was still new and stuff
But it's like I'm kind of shocked at what I've been seeing and it's like I don't know if people are enjoying
Seeing some of this these past episodes or not, but it's like you. Where's your drum at?
It's right around here somewhere
You ever drum with you still it's called the bong
Yeah, I want to
Drum, but yeah, I like the blood bongos
Have you heard of that?
No, I never met him.
I never met him.
I never saw him up here.
And if you've been up here recently, I haven't been watching.
I'm just hearing that.
No, he was on, you know, Sarah's Kitties, that SKG, the Sarah's Kitties show.
No, I don't know Sarah's Kitties.
Listen.
I don't know Suggies.
I don't know Suggies Awakens.
Sarah's show?
Her nickname is B.
Her nickname is Sarah.
I know B.
The show.
I know your show.
That's it.
I don't know what I was talking about.
We met on the Sarah's Kitties show.
Wait, Paige!
Siaki, who is Sarah Kitties, man?
She's Bita. It's Bita.
How do you spell it?
It's Bita, Bita.
Bita, like...
Like, yeah, Bita Juice. No, no, like Bita, like Bita, like she's in, she's in from Iran, she's Persian, so...
Can he show me like, can he, can he show me like her picture or what's, I don't know, I remember like...
I can, I can play you a song about her too. Oh, I have a song to play about her too.
Wanna hear a song about her? Okay, it's real quick.
You said write a funny, cute, loving song about Bita.
She is the host of Beat is Kitty.
She is a beautiful Persian woman.
She is so funny.
She has a hysterical voice.
She is so loyal and true.
I have a BKG tattoo.
Her cats are Mickey and Muhammad.
I will glove her always.
Thank you, Bita.
Sure, here's a funny cute and loving song about beta the host of be asked kiddies with a mix of sweetness laughter and curring kiddies
Think acoustic ukulele or soft indie pop vibe
Thank You beta
You're a Persian queen on screen with cats you're living the dream Mickey and Muhammad at your side
You laugh so loud the stars collide your host beat as kiddies
It's a wild ride with eyeliner sharp and a heart so wide you tell the truth
You never lie even when your cats knock down the Wi-Fi
your shoe she's got sass and she's got style and she can make a troll cry in a
while with just one wink and that Persian grace and a kitty filter on her
face beats as hard as full of gold she'll keep you warm when the world is
cold and when she laughs so man you'll see it's like
and sings along like she's star-
True
Thank you, yeah, what's the name of her channel though? I can't remember the name of her
How do you how do you spell that be ee
TAS
KITT IES
BKG
Beedah's kiddies
Beedah's kiddies BKG
That's her gang name. She's like actually she's like a gang leader of California
She didn't like that picture though. She said it was that she said it didn't look anything like her
She said it looks like some other like race
Now she, I think she might have liked it a little bit.
So we got...
Hey ghost
You just stood up and guys we had a miracle ghost is out of now walking on his wheelchair
I motivated him because he wanted to turn the song off, but it's okay. Whatever works
Miracles of miracle, right
I don't know, it's kind of hard for me to watch myself.
Oh, is Mason here?
Wait, Mason, wait.
It's not hard for me to watch you and watch myself
because I'm like, oh gosh.
I'm like, nobody likes me there.
And it's like, I'm embarrassed of myself.
But you know what?
Maybe I'll embarrass myself so much
that I'll run out of embarrassment to like half.
I don't want to go fucking far.
I'm gonna go to that point.
Let me see if I can find a video.
Let me see.
I'll be there.
Is it this one?
Find a bunch of people like a bunch. I need a bunch. I need like one of those crazy days
Let's beat it right there. So I know you don't realize it's always a good show
Sorry
Psyche!
What's up?
This is my theme song
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Well, I think that's very thick, but why so many Americans stay here, even in Asia, when you cannot trust me.
Sorry, I didn't say I can't trust you. I said that you and me, I said that I would love to go to Indonesia.
I'd love to meet you at Jakarta.
I said that already, but I keep okay, what I'm saying is look you mean you mean when I was I went to
So how are you today?
Yeah, I'm doing okay psyche. What what happened man. I
Was playing you the my theme song and beat is the beat is on you like the beat is kitty song
I'll say what where's uh, where's your other friend that you're talking to in here?
Oh
That was like months. Oh, that was easy. He left and I think he left and
Just me and you in here. It's like wait
So be does be this kiddies you're talking about be this kiddies right on the screen see her on the screen right there
That's her
Can you show me a picture of her? Yeah, she's on the screen. They're black and white photos the black and white
It's like right here. See that right there. I
Can't see can you zoom up or something on it or it's a circle?
Do you see it? Oh shit, it's too big.
Do you see her?
It's really hard to see her. She's like, you know, she's kind of like, she's hard to like
Get a photo. I can play like, I can find a photo of her. If I go to the trip kick, let me see, hold on.
So like, you gotta let me see.
Yeah, you want to see her? Okay, I'll find her one second. I'll get it for one second.
Let me see if I go to each one.
Yeah, you'll see it one second.
I'm going to put this back on, but watch this for a second, I'll be right back.
I'm going to take volumes.
Panels and you me I went to get better at that and it's like don't just say can you know I mean I'll say he can you lower
So yeah, I think you should turn your mic up for everyone
You can post your link. See if you have a channel and most of the people have to see talking to us or she
Be that you're just drunk, so especially I'm happy to help. I think I'm on mushrooms at this point
I'm having out of butter experience and I think like he's talking psyche turn your mic up now
Turn your mic up home today
There's be this there's be the Spanish lesson you're welcome through a charge
testing I can't really I can't really hear what I say I just want to support
no we had nothing you said can you start over again but yeah yeah especially
people like Paige like Paige has started a new channel and you know it's
And you know, of course, beta has a new her new channel is doing like really really well
Piaz still has me bad
Disagree with my old animal who gives a fuck beta you still have me bad
Okay, are you there Mason? Yeah, are you there? Okay, I'm gonna shoot you. Okay. It's very important you watch this, okay?
you'll see be okay looks like but it's very hard to find much it's very rare
you'll see this one second there you go okay you see it on the screen I don't
see it man you know I don't see it oh sorry you don't see anything on the
screen shit no there's nothing on the screen
You see her
E aí
I
Yo psyche I love how you're running your fucking dick fingers in a chat
But you scared to say sign to me when I'm on it on the panel pussy stop talking shit
Why don't you hit the link like you don't run here and stop having you me
So I think you cuz you means a pussy too both y'all can suck my dick from the back hoes
Fuck you talking about you mean like a
You need you need you need keep you need shut the fuck up because you don't know what the fuck is going on
You don't know what the fuck is going on and psyche you a bitch
So if you got something to say hit the panel after you eat bitch
No, because the reason why I'm not and this kind of hurts psyche by the way
What you guys are doing is I'm not gonna pay it because everyone crashes on me because you're trying to control the panel
I didn't name it psyche, I didn't ask psyche to come here or you or none of that.
So whatever goes, whatever the fuck shit goes and people have questions and their opinion, it is not planned.
It just goes.
OK, it's another debate.
So don't say I'm trying to ruin anything.
It's not like the actually it's more advertising.
I've said about twenty dollars to get people kicked off.
But if you were, you don't need some more people here, psyche, psyche, psyche, psyche,
the more they're going to go over there.
It's called fucking promotion, but you don't even get it.
You don't even understand it.
He does terror.
He does terror radius.
And what's good with you mean?
Now you mean the racist and sitting up there
talking about me being black?
You see what you mean?
I thought he was white this whole time.
You mean sitting up there talking about me being black?
What the fuck is this racist shit?
Wait, you mean? Yeah, you mean slayer the catzilla. I
Was good with this this racist shit
Let her explain you want to come up here and see what you mean by that
With you boy
No, what does she mean by that? Yeah, what does that mean? Why what are you trying to say?
I only started saying they're saying that ice and shit. Yeah
Glasses like glasses. That's what no no no no no. Hey, hey, Mesa. Mesa. Do you want to go out? Yeah?
I don't know. I don't know you're here to ask me out. Huh?
Are you here to ask me out?
I was coming to hang out man, but not
Asked out on a like after a new move by a Mason and then like that for a new moon
And it was Mason and I just came single. I just came to be in here
Like I came to come check it out. Do you want to be in my the real place?
fly out here and start a life I
Got it. I got a week. I have a Xbox
You have a what Xbox? Oh
Three six you have a x4. Yeah
It's what games you play everything every game
Every game I got to think about it like say okay
Likey, I mean, it wouldn't be like a slave or anything. You'd be like, you know
I'd let you go like do it and it earns in the neighborhood that you'd be like, you know in my sex slave
Well, well, I gotta you gotta give us some time first like yeah, I mean, okay
Okay, you have three you have three days or else I'm
the offers
You want me to wait for three days to make up my mind?
Well, you tell me you can tell me now, but you have up to three days. Yeah, and if the Sun says I'm a third day
Before you make the decision then you'll be a mermaid forever
I'll be a what a mermaid. You'll turn it back into a mermaid
Well mermaid, why would I be a mermaid?
Oh, hold on, I got, I picked the wrong paper, that was my, that was my Arielle file.
Okay, never mind.
Um, let's see.
I'm just kidding, it's just a joke, I'm just a joke, this is just common.
Hey, Rue, um, raining corn dogs and, uh, Arbiter, Romeo Cross, and Black RG are in here.
And you want to come up on the panel?
Oh, look, there's Saad on the panel.
Saad!
Not porn bomb me, I know who this guy is, he might be porn bomb.
Hold on, I'm forgetting.
Hello?
Are you are you naked you're not naked don't hang up don't hang up. Oh
But are you okay? No, don't form bomb. How are you? Hi?
Hi
So I keep what was that Matthew was the doesn't pervert
And it's like
If you I thought my fever like bad. I like some of my feet today earlier
I when I held them up on camera and they were pretty clean like that was his feet are black on the bottom and I told him not to
So like you what did you do when he came on I turn my head and cover my eyes
Well, he came up and I he like
By the time I like got my finger to the eject button he already had it's naked foot out
showing the camera the whole like
So you weren't expecting anything like that, you know, but can I see your feet?
But you have nice, huh?
You have nice feet
It's like yeah, I don't really show that man. How big are your feet? How many inches?
Me too. We can share they're 13
Now we can like you wear 13's if you meet you if you move in we can share shoes
How tall are you? We you wear the same size shoes? Yeah, we do. We're like really twins
Well, how tall my son?
Yeah, I'm six foot three and I have
Figure your feet psyche. I'm six. I'm six foot two about you. You are we're like twins. Yeah, six foot two
How much do you weigh? I weigh like a hundred and two pounds. How much do I like a two hundred? Oh
That's perfect. Perfect. I
weigh like 200 psych. Yeah, I like a like I'm a little skinny and you're a little bit
Buffed are you just buffed?
Sike, that's me in my picture though. You see my me in my picture, right? You're really cute. You're really cute
So this is what you really look like.
You look kind of like Owen Wilson a little bit.
What do you think, Chad?
Owen Wilson?
Or is it Owen or the, what do you think he looks like, Chad?
Should I start a poll?
Saiki, so what do you think about me, man?
Saiki, what do you think about me?
I want you to have your first gay experience with me.
Like to do that. So so you're gay psyche. You're not straight like you don't you don't go with women like you don't date women
Strictly dickly, huh? Strictly dickly
What do you mean only like men? Yeah
Well, I had like a I had like a girlfriend like you know 2012, which is like 13 years ago
Okay
See you never had experience with a guy like you know in the locker room or something
Not not like gay stuff though. Like not like, you know, like but what do you think like, you know
But what happened though? What happened that wasn't gay, but it was
Why didn't do anything like, you know, like sexual with any guys or anything
No, no with a guy though never a guy with a wig
You sure yeah, I'm telling you truth. Yeah, well, what if I were a wig?
It's hard to say man, I mean I would you let me try one time just one time I
Would have to I would have to see man. I wouldn't tell anybody
I'm a little blowy. Yeah, a little blowy blowy
Not gay if you keep your eyes closed. Oh, yeah, there you go. You're cute. Hello
Psychi so what's going on? I don't know. I like you
It's like what do you think yeah, I think I'm like, yes
No, is that cool like or what what do you think? Yeah, you're cool
You actually think I'm a good guy. Yeah
What what would you like bet?
Just like you can move here and then like, you know, you help me like
My assistant and I like, you know, like I can like, you know, hey you can pay each other in sex
And then, you know, eventually, like, you know, you'll earn enough to, like, buy me a car and then, you know, you can drive me around.
It's like, yeah, play the drums, man. You know I play the drums, right?
Okay, I can use some drum. I know how to market, so I can go, I can take you, I can take you some drumming gigs, and if you want to, like, you know, play the drums on my human body, you can do that too.
If you've ever done that.
Well, how have I done what? It's like, play the drums on someone's body.
I never done that
Yeah, you can try you can never done
Likey, I mean I gotta figure this out man. It's hard to say. Okay, what are you gonna be here?
Don't know
Yeah, I don't know
Yeah, we gotta wait and see man how far away are you?
I'm not that far I don't think
No, Louisiana
But it is kind of farming your own shit. Do you want me to come over there?
We can do Mardi Gras first and then we can now come back here
Yeah, I stay in Louisiana. It's like, okay. Did you go to Mardi Gras? I
Go to Mardi Gras. Yeah
Okay, I'm gonna go with me. You can get my tour guide to see if it works out. Yeah
Okay
Where will I sleep?
Huh, where will I sleep? I go there
You got to figure that out man. You got to find a place for that to have to
Yeah, you have a room in your bed
Yeah, you could probably do that
Okay
I'll sleep in your bed. I'm gonna sleep on the street. It's fine.
I'm just kidding, but I do unless you're like, you know, you're like you're like you have all your marbles, right? You're not like
You know, you're not any like violence counseling or like, no
I don't have what what do you mean? Do I have all my marbles psyche? What do you mean by that?
Do you have like are you a criminal record or anything?
No, I don't have a criminal record. No
You never never killed anybody or hurting anybody real bad or anything. No, I've never done that stuff
I never killed anybody or hurt you by nothing like you never would right you never would right?
No, I wouldn't do that. Yeah, I don't do stuff like that
Well, that sounds like we're a match in that department.
I don't know, but if you like to kill it, I'll kill it.
So, Aki, what kind of games do you play?
I play on the VR, you know and you know I play on I actually have over a thousand other games
I have a game called don't feed the monkeys. It says too bad. You don't live closer. We could jam. Yeah, Randy
I mean, it's like I live in LA. So it's not too far
He's lying. What's why is he lying about mr. Total? How do you know this guy? It says the crazy ones are always the best in bed
Yeah, well, I hoping that I mean he seems like I want to find him. Yeah, I do want someone a little bit crazy
I just don't want him, I don't want to like...
I don't want you to be too innocent, but you're not, you're not, you're not like, are you that innocent or like, no?
Cause it's like, I don't want to corrupt anybody, I want to like...
No, psyche, yeah, I'm innocent, man. Yeah.
You're innocent? Okay, you probably should stay away from me, cause that's like, I'm like, I'm too, I'm too like, not innocent for first time.
I don't know how to put it. No, I mean, I am innocent, but it's like, I don't know, you'll do the same thing.
I am here to leave your innocent here. Oh
Those don't have a threesome. So would you if we had a threesome you'd want like a female there, right?
Yeah
And what would I be doing on that scenario?
It's up to you, man. Okay. Okay. I know. I like how you think so you're open to whatever I want whatever we want to do
Yeah, if you if you agree at the time, okay, it's perfect. You figure out what you want to do. That's what that's what you gotta do
Okay, I figured out I don't have an idea. Yeah. Wow. Oh, okay
Yeah, I do want to come out
So when should I book your plane to this guy? I think I found the perfect guy. Is this a perfect guy guys?
I think especially for me
This is perfect guys. I always wanted to
That I don't like I don't like how he just disappears right when I'm like getting somewhere he just disappears
And he said I could do anything I want
Guys, does that sound like a perfect guy?
So...
Super attractive.
Mason, come back!
Fuck.
Gone.
I'll play some music until he comes back.
Guys, get him back here or else the music will...
Said it came through with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones are drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the big off crew, but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron cardamom rose water drizzle you brought confusion and a half-baked fizzle
I'm the biscuit of Babylon
I
Fuck all that shit. No, she said I have to mention something about
Yeah, I'm not making a document for her. She's probably, I know what she meant.
Tell me from you, Yumi, that always acts like you're all about peace and equality and let's love each other and you know, you know, you're a Muslim and just come on. Like, are you serious?
So second time you actually maybe more than I've ever known that you did this like you
store on the Quran before about something and I definitely went back and I showed it
to you and you apologized to me.
So you want to apologize to Bronzeberg because or explain what you actually said.
forgive her but I just don't like fucking fake like she always does this like she'll be like
message me or like oh this is what I meant or I'm sorry miss Vita or this and this and that
get your fucking balls together and come up here and say what the fuck you meant period okay or
don't come in here go and like just hide don't say that anybody else is a liar you're lying
gonna ban you, but I'm gonna call you racist. I am. I'm gonna
call you a hypocritical fucking ignorant bitch that sits up
there, putting a smile on her fucking face, reading the chat,
not giving a fuck about psyche or anybody else but themselves
trying to look for anybody that fucking even mentions them,
you attention seeking fucking bitch. That's what I'm gonna do.
Okay.
You're gonna stand that she was talking about black Archie.
She's no you don't get to come back here like that. You just
That's what she said everybody send you a screenshot of what she really said what is she what did you say?
I would I would agree with that bronze bird. I don't want to talk to you face-to-face. You're black
Hold on. Oh, she's she's stripping about yeah, I know she's stripping about
Don't ever fucking you're gonna believe her over me
No, I was on the panel. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you.
Did say you may bring to your fucking plate. What? Why are you yelling for? What?
Yeah, I'm looking for the comment. Let me see. She said that every single funnel,
like every single one of my good friends that you ever known and met was because of me.
I will tell you, you know, if not one of them,
I don't want to fuck with that fucking crazy bitch.
She said, race is crazy shit in the past.
She said, crazy shit in the past.
She's nuts.
She's crazy.
You want to be with her, you want to be with racist people?
No, no, oh my God, oh my God.
Yeah.
We want Bronzeberg, not you.
I've given you the filter.
I already told you who's cool, who's not.
And you're like, Vita, you're right.
They were cool to me.
They were nice to me.
You want to listen to me? Okay. So I'm gonna give you a choice right now. You really think that you're gonna believe me over fucking Yumi or Viva
Alright you guys we're gonna talk about everybody on my panel, everybody can call him a scammer, call him a fucking grifter, anything because he loves racist people. He's a racist lover. Yes. He
People fucking talk to Bronzeberg like that one of my fucking mods. That is black. Fuck you and you're fucking you
You are being toxic and you will be back in a couple minutes and you will apologize. Why are you being so toxic? That was crazy
I don't know what I was thinking. I know your sister bro, don't give into that. That was crazy
I'm looking right now
She said if she said I can throw your payment. She said if you don't do this, I'm gonna do this
How crazy was oh my god, you clip it in the ship brother. That was fucking crazy. Do you not agree that was crazy?
Well, then I couldn't respond that I'm not like able to like, you know, say one word.
I'm just like, she'll scream at me and that's it.
If you weren't even there, if you don't respond with that person,
Yumi said that when you were gone, by the way, she said something about being black to Brownsburg.
It was like, I'm not going to talk, I don't even know what the fuck that person said.
That was crazy. She came, she talked about running your panel.
She just came over and tried to do that. She said, if you don't do this, I'm going to do this.
Disrespectful she should come over and apologize to be honest with you. I mean, I'll be real with you. She should apologize
Okay, you know what? I
Need apologies is like
Well, don't come over talking shit though be peaceful that was crazy she never touched it
If you do this psyche, I'm gonna do this
Crazy
You know what I'm against racism and I say, you know
You maybe we're saying something about race isn't like that
That's just like it opens you up to be attacked and stuff like that. I know you don't mean it
Do you mean the different race than?
Me right you made a different race like we're all different races all the human race, right?
So I don't I don't know it's like and I don't want to fight with
Good I'm pretty sure this piano is open. I'm pretty sure whoever wants as long as you get along with it can join
So a baby Vita
I'm putting it up. Vita's is running her own show and I don't know why she's like is it you mean?
Everything everybody else
Anyone that was just talking about shit about psych fucking joined the panel. Let's run that
You need to recharge over me. He's like, all right, you know how many people I even fucking you he's like
And he like puts his hands together like I'm like begging petty whatever
Let me tell you I've defended you so much tonight every time I fucking lose the panel no more
So that's I keep fucking and that's actually me good. I didn't do anything wrong. Just in that the fuck you're talking about
You literally left my panel you joined my panel have like over a hundred people here
We're all fucking just chillin doing our own fucking thing and then all of a sudden one or two people
Say something about you and you're like
Going like having like, oh my god, I'm gonna go hide behind the covers
You fail to see what some of your fucking mods are saying about other people about my mods. Okay?
You meet
Yikes
She fucking literally sat there and like like was racist in my fucking chat and he just dismisses it
And then if somebody's in his chat, I knew me is like somebody even says like oh, you know
Here comes you me again
She'll just time him out and I see it constantly over and over like her being super fucking sensitive
Lying hypocritical retarded ass fucking bitch
Imagine when somebody like psyche who fucking like
Literally literally got a tattoo of my fucking like BKG on his chest is gonna fucking take you me after me
We'll eat that fucking shit then get the fuck away from me
All right, is that true psyche? Did you actually get that every fucking week after deal with him?
I'm sorry ask. Oh my god. You're hurting my fucking brand. You're hurting my fucking pocket. Well, do a better job at it
I'm not like what do I think I'm working fucking extra time to try to protect your fucking logo? What the fuck do you do for me?
The huh
It's like you did you say yeah insanity
Oh my God! I'm gonna fix him again! Oh no! Oh no! Somebody is like trying to take food out of my fucking mouth!
The hell? Get a fucking job!
I mean get a part-time one like we can all use a little bit of extra fucking money
What the hell did I do for you like I to you'd all I did was fucking like promote you send people to your fucking chat
Like fucking forgave you, you know every time you play fucking victim like I just let us live by people are like beta
Press them press them and I'm like now. I'm over it
I come up there and you're like fucking like letting this fucking rich hearted bitch named fucking you me the fucking lying. I have like screenshots of her like begging be done. I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to fucking like, you know, like swear on my Quran on her Quran about fucking lies.
I started my life, and I was having a great fucking time without you.
Hey, Ron, what's up?
Yeah, yeah.
No, I mean, you can still get your shit off. Don't fall asleep, you know?
No, I'm good. Uh, I just want to know, what the fuck did he not leave you on?
Like, you just went up there and he just didn't let you on for no reason?
No, no, he let me on. I was talking my shit.
Yumi, Yumi was basically making it seem like, yeah, I said it, I said it, so what?
And so basically I was just going off when she changed her story three times first she said it was about she said she didn't say it
Then she said she was talking about black rg and now she's saying that she said it so what okay
Yeah, that's full of shit because black rg was barely even in the chat. You only said one thing in the chat
I read that fucking sentence six times at least right exactly. She said two things to me about about black
You saw me and I saw it and I'm just like yo, so what the fuck why are you saying racist shit?
I didn't keep it as like on issues like oh, I don't like how you you was talking about psyche blah blah blah
And I'm like, okay, and
You're gonna fucking like resort to fucking being a racist bitch, exactly
The big master defender of fucking LD 15 to a fucking tea like it is like he
is, she's unreasonable, she's fucking crazy.
Just like Justin that's why you like her she likes dogs you know Justin fucks dogs
So, now we're just talking about fucking animals.
Yeah, you like to fuck animals because you fucking.
I've never, I've never had sex with a.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
I don't give a shit. The more you guys give her credit for her cuteness on her, you know, just like being funny, she's gonna get worse and worse.
Like, like for real, for real, be like, yeah, she's pretty and everything, but her fucking mind, she's fucking.
crazy. Yeah, she needs to chill the fuck out, dude. Like,
I'm not dealing with that. I'm not here.
How about you fucking Sam? She said that you fuck your fucking
cat. I'm defending you. So don't defend anybody else. You want
to be booted up? You can go and talk to her privately about how
thick she thinks you are.
I'm not in the mood for this shit. Good time. You want it? You want it?
You're acting like I give a fuck.
Hey, Psyche, can you call this real quick?
Who raised you? Who fucking raised you?
Oh my god.
And I appreciate you for having me up. Somebody said I should join.
Oh, you're good, really.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I appreciate you grabbing me up somebody said I should join I was just confused about
What we're doing should I because we were watching those clips and stuff should I have like some feedback because I can watch
Okay, that's what I was asked nice I wasn't sure what we were doing, but yeah continue man, I just that was my question
It's fine. Uh, can we watch it and then can we react to it? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Let's go
Nice
I don't give a fuck if you're my fucking sister or anybody else.
You talk like that about my brother.
You just shut your fucking mouth.
You talk a lot of fucking crap because you think you're a crystal marine, right?
You can fucking just say like people are, you know, they were fucking cat efforts, whatever. And you think it's all cool. But if somebody else does something, you're going to like hold them accountable for the rest of your life.
Oh, this guy wanted to say this.
Don't come crying and say be that treated me like shit cuz that's what you should be treated like after what you fucking say you're literally shit
And I'm backstage always
You're fucking dumb whore, I hope you my picture
Then sit here with shit like you your trash
your trash. I can say everything to you except for fucking talk about your family, your pets, and like, accuse you and put jackets on you. Your trash. That's what you resort to. That's what you are. Your little tear trash.
Say weird
Yeah, I don't like that shit. I don't give a fuck if it was you
I don't give a fuck you with clumsy war my worst enemy
You're not gonna sit here and have like this weird imaginative thought of saying you fuck your fucking cat
But though you're weird you're weird
You're weird weird
No one even fucking right my like listen I get drunk all the time. I wild out the kind of shit you say are far
fucking weird
To anybody in the chat and the mod stuff. Yeah, we are live. It's actually live. We're just watching order stuff
Well, we are alive right now
Talk about cats, don't accuse even good times.
Who the hell brought fucking heaven's section?
Oh, that's right, that's right.
What are you gonna say next?
What are you gonna say?
Well, you have fucking like people
like you should fucking not be around
because you can't fucking control your mouth.
You're disgusting.
BKG always will stand up for cats always shut your fucking mouth you fucking weirdo
Who would say that?
Who would fucking say that? Oh, guess what we're gonna have some vampires fucking
Thirsty as dog like some I say it's not a big deal
Yeah, but lovers
People being catfuckers you bitch
So you dumb bitch. So be out of here trash bitch. You're fucking a lunatic. You're a lunatic. At the end of the day, Crystal, I would not come near you. I wouldn't be friends with you in real life. I wouldn't hang out with you because you're probably crazy. I'll hang out with you online. That's about it. After what you fucking just said, I don't want nothing.
Nothing's ever to meet you in real life.
You can always hang out with me on our panel,
but you're a lunatic.
Wow.
Not so crazy.
Sherryl.
You don't hear me saying that about a lot of people.
You hear me saying that about like,
hmm, that's like me, Tracy.
Was she talking about that dude at the bottom?
No, you're stupid
Samon will dismiss it because all he cares about is fucking this and that
All right, that's all he cares about what he can get it doesn't fucking matter crystal is beautiful
She's top of the line when it comes to looks on the fucking panel verse
He's always gonna be a thirsty ass dog and she's dumb enough to fucking you that people really care about her
You think I don't fucking know the reality?
Why do you think I would cry for myself?
The fuck?
She can say whatever, and it's excuse.
But if I have somebody on my panel say something to him,
not even me, I'm responsible.
If somebody calls this man a fucking PDF like Samma,
it wasn't even me.
I'm responsible for years and years.
Hold on guys want
Okay
guys
Beated told me not to use her content. So even though it's on
Even though it's on trip kick right now, and this is like somebody else using your content. I'm not allowed to so
You know, I wasn't trying to make her like that. I was just
But it's okay. I understand she said no, so I took it off immediately. I'll probably just end my stream